乔伊 你可以慢一点吗?
Joey, would you slow down?
报纸不会在凌晨一点就卖光的
They're not gonna be sold out of papers at 1:00 in the morning.
我好兴奋 第一次有对我的剧评
I'm excited. I've never gotten reviewed before.
你国王演得太精彩了 我很欣赏你 真的
You were so amazing as the king. I'm really impressed. I was.
不过你知道吗
Although, you know what?
我觉得你下次得考虑穿条内裤
You might wanna consider wearing underwear next time.
因为当你登上宝座的时候 大家都能看到你的...
Yeah, cuz when you down sat on your throne, you could kind of see your...
龙根
royal subjects.
有了 在这儿
Here it is. Here it is.
"唯一比脑残弱智导演还要烂的"
"The only thing worse than the mindless, adolescent direction..."
"是乔伊崔比亚尼 对国王毫无技巧的诠释
"was Joseph Tribbiani's disturbingly unskilled portrayal of the king."
别灰心啦 这只是一家之见
Okay, look, that is one guy's opinion, all right?
菲比 念你的      好
Pheebs, read yours.        Okay.
"唯一比脑残弱智导演还要烂的..."
"The only thing worse than the mindless, adolescent direction..."
拜托哪位大哥念下别家的报纸好吗
Does anybody have one from a different paper?
罗斯 念你的
Ross, read yours.
我不想念
I don't want to.
乔伊 他们不知道自己在说什么
Joey, honey, they don't know what they're talking about.
就是说呀
Yeah.
也许他们说的是有道理的
Maybe they do.
哥在演艺圈混了十年了 还没混出什么名堂
I've been doing this 10 years, and I haven't gotten anywhere.
不是因为我烂是什么
There's gotta be a reason.
别这样嘛 就当现在是在交学费
Oh, come on, man, you're just, uh, you're just paying your dues.
不 这真的是太难了
No, no, no. It's... it's too hard.
这不值得 我不干了
It's not worth it. I quit.
不是吧      你疯了
What?        That's crazy.
等等 别急
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, one minute. Wait a minute.
这评论包你听了回心转意
I believe this will change your mind.
"在这出平凡的戏里"
"In a mediocre play"
"乔伊崔比亚尼成功地跃上另一境界..."
"Joseph Tribbiani was able to achieve brilliant new levels of..."
接153页...
Continued on page 153...
"烂透了"
"sucking."
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第10集
罗斯的翻版  The One With Russ
调校制作：海盗美剧 寒 枫
字幕编辑：海盗美剧 yjchandler
小时候 我的梦想是当兽医
When I was little, I wanted to be a veterinarian.
但后来我发现 兽医得把手伸进那些动物的身体里
But then I found out you had to put your hands into cows and stuff.
哎...
Hi...
嘿
Hey.
怎么啦
Are... are you okay?
没什么 也就是个水深火热的一天
Yeah, yeah, just a tough day at work, you know?
一副剑龙的骨架倒下来 困住了一个孩子
A stegosaurus fell over, trapped a kid.
哇哦 我认得这件夹克 是搞笑巴比的
Whoa, whoa, I know this jacket, this is, the Fun Bobby's jacket!
他在哪儿 他在这儿 对不对
Where is he? What... he's here, isn't he?
你猜呀      别耍我
Maybe.        Don't toy with me.
盖勒!      嘿 搞笑巴比
Geller!        Hey, Fun Bobby.
嘿 你有去健身哦
Hey. Whoa, hey, you've been working out, huh?
才没有
Not at all.
我爱这家伙
I love this guy.
知道你和我妹妹复合真是太高兴了
I was so psyched to hear you're back with my sister.
我也是      我错过了什么 快说
You and me both.        So, what'd I miss, what'd I miss? Come on.
我们只是想让乔伊好过一点
Oh, we were just trying to make Joey feel better.
要不要我把你抱起来
Hey, do you need me to pick you up?
不 我没事 真的
No, I'm all right, man, really.
不 我要把你抱起来
No, I'm picking you up.
不 说真的 真的不用...
Hey, no, seriously. I don't need you to pick me...
好吧 这招还是很有用
All right, it still works.
好啦 在我走之前 还有谁想让我抱起来的
Okay, now, before I go, does anybody else need to be picked up?
我还是走好了
I'm still gonna go.
好啦 待会儿见 宝贝儿
Okay, I'll... I'll see you later, babe.
我们要公开亲热 你们可以回避一下
Public display of affection coming up. You can avert your eyes.
再见      再见      待会儿见
See you.        Bye.        See you later.
搞笑巴比真棒
Fun Bobby is so great.
可不是嘛
Oh, isn't he?
我觉得这次我们是有未来的
Oh, you know, I really think this time it may work with him.
他让我觉得很开心
I mean he just makes me feel so good.
这两个月我一直感觉很糟
And I've been feeling so lousy, you know, this last couple of months.
既没工作也没爱情
No job, no boyfriend.
但至少现在我有了一样
Well, at least my cup is half full.
有了爱...情
Half full of looooove.
为了庆祝我们的两周庆
And for our two-week anniversary
周末他要带我去他表哥的小木屋
he's gonna take me to his cousin's cabin for the weekend.
爱...的小屋
Cabin of looooove.
我们今晚喝了好多酒
We went through a lot of wine tonight, you guys.
不是吧 我才喝了两杯
Really? I only had two glasses.
我只喝了一杯
I just had a glass.
我两杯
Two.
我就一杯
I had one glass.
我用这个可爱的...写着 "我在自然历史
I had about a mug full in this lovely...
博物馆看到骨头了" 的马克杯喝了一杯
"I got boned at the Museum of Natural History" mug.
这么说的话 最多两瓶
Okay, so that's... that's what, two bottles.
可是这里有五个空酒瓶
And yet somehow we went through five?
原来如此
Oooooh.
对噢
Oh!
那又怎样 他只不过今晚喝多了
So what? So he drank a lot tonight.
是呀 但我现在回想起来
Yeah, but, you know, now that I think about it
搞笑巴比从来酒不离手
I don't think I've ever seen Fun Bobby without a... a drink in his hand.
对啊
Yeah. Oh, oh, yeah, you know
你们有没有注意过 他故事的开头总是
Did you notice how he always starts his stories with, um...
"我当时醉醺醺的" 或是 "我们都喝高了"
"Okay, I was so wasted" or "Oh, we were so bombed"
又或是 "醒来时 发现我在康州的一个垃圾站里"
Or, um, oh oh, "So I wake up and I'm in this dumpster in Connecticut."
摩妮卡 你们约会时他有不喝酒的时候吗
Monica, have you ever been with him when he wasn't drinking?
没有 但那只是恰巧我们去的地方都会喝酒
Well, we just happen to go to a lot of places where you might drink.
我是说比如品酒会 去了总要喝上一杯吧
I mean, how do you go to a wine-tasting without having a drink?
还有夜店 或者是...
Or, or to a club, or to the...
动物园
zoo.
谢啦 瑞秋 这里面有脱脂牛奶吗
Thanks. Rach, does this have nonfat milk?
呃... 不知道 你尝尝看
Ehhhummmm, I... I don't know, why don't you taste it?
没有
Mm, no.
太迟啦 不能换了 你已经喝过啦
Oh, well, too late, sorry, you already had some.
我们把它弄成爱尔兰式咖啡 怎么样
What do you say we make these, uh, coffees, Irish?
呃... 我要蛋糕!
Um, cake!
对 我们来吃点蛋糕
Yeah, we're gonna... we're gonna get some cake.
那什么
You know what
最近你似乎把太多的东西都弄成了爱尔兰风味的
it seems like you've been making an awful lot of stuff Irish lately.
我也想弄成比利时风味的
Well, I would make them Belgian
但是这华夫饼很难塞进酒壶
but the waffles are hard to get into that flask.
拜托 巴比
Bobby.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
听着 这或许不关我的事
Look, maybe this is none of my business,
或许又和我有关 我不清楚
or, maybe it is, I don't know.
但我有点担心你
But, um, I'm kind of worried about you.
好吧 是这样
Okay, look
这不是第一次有人和我提这事了
this isn't the first time somebody said something to me about this.
但我总是为自己找些借口
But, I don't know, I always made excuses about it
像 "我只是交际一下"
like "I'm just a social drinker."
或者是 "拜托 国旗日总得喝点吧"
Or "Hey, come on, it's Flag Day."
那你现在有什么想法
So, what are you saying now?
我想说的是...
I guess I'm saying...
我会试着戒酒
I'll try and quit.
我挺喜欢你担心我的样子
I kinda like that you worry about me.
发生什么事啦
So, what's going on?
我呢 会试着戒酒
I, am gonna try and quit drinking.
这是为什么
Oh! Why?
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
猜猜谁又回演艺圈了
Guess who's back in show business.
洛恩格林吗
Ooh, ooh. Lorne Greene?
不 菲比 不是 知道为什么吗 因为他早死了
No, no, Pheebs. You know why? Because he's dead.
不是吧
Oh, no.
好吧 我猜这似乎有点喜忧参半
Okay, I guess this is gonna seem bittersweet now
是乔伊 就是他
but Joey, that's who!
太棒了      真的吗
Oh, yay!        Really?
是真的 经纪人要我去 "我们的日子" 试镜
Yeah, my agent just called me with an audition for "Days of Our Lives" !
帅呆了
Kick ass!
我们得庆祝下
Oh, well, we have to celebrate.
知道我们该干嘛吗 开一个肥皂剧主题的派对
You know what we should do? We should do, like, a soap opera theme.
对 我们可以睡一块儿
Hey, yeah. We could all sleep together
然后其中一人可以忘掉这一切
and then one of us could get amnesia.
瑞秋 你几点下班 今晚一起活动
Hey Rach, what time do you get off? We're all gonna do something tonight.
其实我已经下班了 但我有其他打算了
Um, well, actually, I'm already done. Ahem, but I... I kind of got plans.
你居然还有其他朋友
You have other friends?
我有个约会
Yeah, I, uh, I have a date.
什么
What?
跟男人?
With a man?
干嘛 我有约会很奇怪吗
What? What is so strange about me having a date?
那罗斯怎么办?
What about Ross?
我的意思是 你还在为他列的关于你的单子生气吗
I mean, are you still mad at him cuz he made that list about you?
不 我没有生他气
No, no, I'm not mad at him.
我再也不会对他有什么感情了
I'm... I'm not really anything at him anymore.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我也不清楚
I don't know, I...
不管我以前对罗斯是什么感觉 但现在...
What... whatever I was feeling, I'm...
不是了
not.
可你们就差一步啊
But you guys came so close.
我明白 抱歉 伙计们
Oh I know, I'm sorry, you guys.
你们要试着接受
You're just gonna have to get used to the fact
我和罗斯已经分手了这个事实
that I will not be dating Ross.
他来了 嗨
Here he is. Hi.
伙计们 这是洛斯
Guys, this is Russ.
嗨...
Hi...
不不不 我不是说你没才华 你很有才华
No, no no no no. I'm not saying you're not talented. You're very talented.
只是那只鸟死了之后 剩下的戏就很少了
It's just with the bird dead and all, there's very little act left.
亲爱的 饶了我吧 好吗
Oh, honey, give me a break, will you?
等下 我待会儿打给你
Oh, oh. I'll talk to you later.
瞧瞧 是我最爱的客户来了
Well, there's my favorite client.
告诉我 亲爱的 试镜结果怎么样
So tell me, darling, how was the audition?
我觉得挺顺利的 他们要我周四去复试
Well, I think it went pretty well. I... I got a callback for Thursday.
乔伊 你看过我欣喜若狂的表情吗
Joey! Have you ever seen me ecstatic?
没有
No.
那就让你见识见识
Well, here it is.
不错 呃 是这样 有件事我想和你谈谈
Okay, uh, listen, there's something I want to talk to you about.
那位电台选角的女士
The network casting lady...
罗莉很可爱吧
Oh isn't Lori a doll?
对 她很棒 但是...
Oh yeah, yeah, she's great, but...
我觉得她好像... 对我有点意思
I kinda got the feeling that she was sort of... coming on to me.
我觉得如果我想得到那个角色 我就得 你懂的...
And, I definitely would get the part if I were to... you know...
如果我愿意单枪赴会
If I would've sent the little general in.
天呐
Oh.
明白了 好吧 我现在就打个电话
I see. Well, I'm just gonna put in a call here
把事情搞清楚 看看究竟是怎么回事
and we'll find out what's going on and straighten it out.
喂 你好 麻烦让罗莉接电话
Yeah, hi. Lori, please.
亲爱的
Hi, darling.
乔伊崔比亚尼适不适合 出租车司机的角色
So how about Joey Tribbiani for the part of the cab driver?
他表现很棒吧
Isn't he terrific?
嗯哼...
Uh-huh...
对
Uh-huh.
好的 美女 待会儿聊
Okay, doll, talk to you later.
对 她要潜规则你
Yeah, you're gonna have to sleep with her
怎么啦?
What's the matter?
还不是巴比
Fun Bobby.
怎么了 他不是没喝酒吗
What? Isn't he sober?
确实没喝
Oh, he's sober all right.
只是我发现 巴比搞笑是有原因的
Just turns out that Fun Bobby was fun for a reason.
噢 明白了
Ah... okay.
拿去吧 亲爱的
All right, here you go, sweetie.
谢谢 要不要听个搞笑的事
Thanks. You wanna hear something funny?
天啊 当然
Oh, God, yes.
这附近的五金店一过半夜就全关门了
There are no hardware stores open past midnight in the Village.
好好笑哦
That is funny.
几天前的晚上我要买把榔头
I needed to buy a hammer the other night
我就出门到附近逛逛
and I'm out walking around the neighborhood.
但显然...
But apparently...
这附近的五金店一过半夜就全关门了
there are no hardware stores open past midnight in the Village.
呃 亲爱的 你现在不是该去面试了吗
Uh, say, honey, don't you have to be at your interview now?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
再见各位
See you guys.
再见...
Bye...
无聊到令人发指的巴比
Ridiculously dull Bobby.
无法想象
Oh, my God.
还没那么糟啦
He's not that bad.
没那么糟? 你没听到他买榔头的事吗
Not that bad? Did you not hear the hammer story?
好吧 别那么挑剔嘛
Okay, okay, don't get all squinky.
也许你该亲身经历才会觉得那个故事好笑啊
Maybe, it was just the kind of story where you had to be there.
我会亲身经历的
But I'm gonna be there.
我下半辈子都会
For the rest of my life.
我没办法跟他分手 是我要他戒酒的
I mean, I can't break up with him. I'm the one who made him quit drinking.
他变得无趣完全是因为我
He's dull because of me.
嘿 别这么说
All right, don't say that.
也许他一向很无趣 你只是... 那个什么
He's probably always been dull. You just... you know...
把他从无趣中解放出来了
set it free.
嗨
Hi.
嘿 罗斯... 嚯!
Hey Ross... Bahhhh!
嗨 洛斯
Hi, Russ.
我再把两张桌子擦干净就能走了 好吗
I've just got two more tables to clean, and then we'll go, okay?
好 我就坐在这里...
Okay. I'll just sit here and, uh...
跟这些...
chat with your, uh...
似乎是你朋友的人聊聊天
friend-type people.
瑞秋
Rachel?
方便聊聊吗
Um, hi.
怎么了
Hi.
你知道你在做什么吧
Okay, so you know what you're doing, right?
服务员?
Uh... waitressing?
好吧 我的意思是 呃...
Well, yeah, but... no. I mean, um...
洛斯有没有让你想起某人
doesn't... doesn't Russ just remind you of someone?
鲍伯萨格特?
Huh, Bob Saget?
对哦
Oh, yeah!
不不不 不是这个意思
Oh, no no no no no, oh, oh.
嗨
Hi.
我了个去啊
Oh, my, oh.
怎么了
What? What's wrong?
我... 好吧 是这样...
I... okay...
她不开心是因为
She's just upset because she, uh
她今早把一只蜘蛛涂在吐司上了 没注意吃掉了
She buttered a spider into her toast this morning.
了解
Mm-hm.
好吧
All right.
听着 菲比 没关系的
Listen, Pheebs, this is gonna be okay.
罗斯 这是洛斯 洛斯 这是罗斯
Ross, Russ. Russ, Ross.
你好      你好
Hi.        Hi.
你是 呃 瑞秋的朋友吗
Are you a, uh, friend of Rachel's?
是啊
Yes, yes I am.
你是 呃 瑞秋的朋友吗
Are you a, uh, friend of Rachel's?
事实上 我是 呃
Actually, I'm uh...
应该算是 呃
kind of a...
瑞秋 呃
you know, uh...
约会的 呃
date-type thing...
对象
of Rachel's.
约会?
A date?
对 和我约会
Yeah, I'm her date.
你和...
Oh, oh, you're, uh...
你和... 她约会
Oh, you're the date.
这其实挺好的
You know, this is actually good...
因为万一我们失去罗斯 还有个备胎
because if we ever lose Ross, we have a spare.
噢 你就是那个 呃 古生物学家
Oh, you are the, uh... paleontologist.
是的 我是 而你是...
Yes, yes I am. And you are a...
牙科医师
Periodontist.
瞧 现在他们简直是黑夜和...
See? Now they're as different as night and...
更黑的夜
later that night.
那好 我要去 呃 买杯饮料
Well, I am going to, uh... get a beverage. Heh.
很高兴 呃 认识你      彼此
Uh, it was nice, nice... uh... meeting you.        Ditto.
我 呃 我见过 呃 洛斯了
I, uh, well... I... I met Russ.
好啊
Oh.
我怎么不知道 呃 我们还能和其他人约会
Hey, I didn't know we were, uh, seeing other people.
既然我们没有在交柱 所以...      哈
Well, we're not seeing each other, so...        Huh.
那好 我跟你说哦 我们馆里有个女的
Well, uh, for your information, there's a woman at the museum
负责蛾类还有其他...
who's curator of moths and other, uh...
有翅生物
winged things...
众所周知 她痴迷于我 就像是
who's, uh, let it be known that she is drawn to me, much like a...
你 你知道的
well, you know. Ahem.
至今我一直跟她保持距离 但如果你要这样的话
Well, so far I've been keeping her at bay, but, uh, if this is the deal
是的 没错
Well, yeah, this is the deal.
好吧 晚上玩得开心      谢谢
Okay, well, um, have a nice evening.        Thank you.
洛斯 可以走了吗      走吧
Um, Russ, you ready?        Yeah.
再见      再见
Bye.        Bye.
她约会了?
She's dating?
她就这么开始约会了?
对 但你看到她在跟谁约会了吗?
Yes, yes, but did you see who she was dating?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你看不出来吗
Do you not see it?
看个球啊
See what?
真搞不懂 她看中那傻帽哪一点
I don't know what she sees in... innnnn that goober.
那家伙讲完一句话 差不多要
And it takes him, what? Like... like... I don't know, uhh...
拜托 难道要 一个礼拜吗
uh, hello... a... week, to get out a sentence.
是啊 烦死人了 是吧
Yeah, it's annoying, isn't it?
对啊
Yeah.
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
喔噢 怎么回事
Whoa, whoa.
我猜你是没拿到那个角色
So I'm guessing you didn't get the part
还是意大利打电话来说它饿了
or uh... Italy called and said it was hungry?
不 我要的话那角色肯定是我的
Well, the part's mine if I want it.
不是吧
Oh, my God.
没错 只要我愿意被选角的女士潜规则
Yeah, if I'm willing to sleep with the casting lady.
哦 不是...
Oh, my...
吧
God?
这十年来我一直在等 像这样的机会 钱德 十年啊
Ten years I've been waiting for a break like this, Chandler, ten years!
那可是 "我们的日子"  那真的会在电视上播的
I mean, "Days of Our Lives". That's actually on television.
那你要怎么做
So, what are you gonna do?
我可以跟她上床 但是...
I guess I could sleep with her, I mean...
我怎么能那么做
How can I do that?
我有本立体书 我能从上面知道一切关于性爱的事
Well, I... I've got a pop-up book that told me everything I need to know.
我从来没为了一个角色跟别人上过床
I've never slept with someone for a part.
那她...
Well, is she...
抱歉
Sorry.
没事儿
It's alright.
她漂亮吗      好看
Is she good-looking?        Yeah.
非常漂亮 如果我是在酒吧之类的地方碰到她
She's totally good-looking. I mean, if I met her in a bar or something...
我一定会请她吃早餐
I'd be buying her breakfast.
跟她上床之后 你明白吧
You know, after having slept with her.
或许这没什么大不了的
You know, maybe this isn't such a big deal.
依我看 你不但能得到一份好工作
I mean, the way that I see it is, you get a great job and
还能有性生活
you get to have sex.
你想想 再加上一棵树一个胖子 就是在过圣诞节了
You know, I mean, throw in a tree and a fat guy, and you've got Christmas.
我只是不想用那样的方式得到这份工作 明白吗
I just... I just don't think that I want it that way, though, you know?
我是说 如果有一天我真的成功了
I mean, let's say I do make it, all right?
我会怀疑那到底是因为我的才华
I'm always gonna look back and wonder if it was because of my talent...
还是因为 你懂的 我的这杆长枪
or because of... you know, the little general.
你以前不是用短枪的吗
Didn't you used to call it "the little major" ?
是啊 但在丹妮丝帝马可后 我就把它升级了
Yeah, but after Denise DeMarco, I had to promote it.
要来点喝的吗
Can I get you something from the bar?
好 我要点杯酒
Yes, I would like something.
还是不了 谢谢
No, no, thank you.
没关系 你想喝酒的话 我没问题
If... if you wanna drink, it's okay with me.
我必须要习惯这样
I've got to get used to it.
不 真的 我也觉得我说的不合时宜
No, no, really. I... I wouldn't feel right about it.
来杯水吧 谢谢
Just some water, please.
我冰箱里的灯坏了...
So the light went out in my refrigerator...
来杯威士忌加冰块跟柠檬
I'd like a scotch on the rocks with a twist.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这游戏很有趣吧 罗斯?
Hey, we're having some fun now, huh, Ross?
再做一个好不好 洛斯?
Wanna do another one? Huh, Russ?
好吧 11个字母
Okay... eleven letters
元素周期第101位 以 "ium" 结尾
atomic element number 101, ends in "ium".
镝
Dysprosium.
镝你个头
应该是钔
Try mendelevium.
小熊维尼二号答对了
And Weenie number two has it.
除非第九列的
Unless, of course nine-down
"白缎骑士" 是杜迪布鲁斯唱的
"Knights in White Satin" was sung by the Doody Blues.
你看不出来吗 你真的看不出来吗
You don't see it? You actually don't see it?
看出来什么
What?
你在跟罗斯约会
Okay, honey, you're dating Ross.
不 菲比 我跟洛斯约会
No, Pheebs, I'm dating Russ.
洛斯就是罗斯 洛斯 罗斯
Russ is Ross. Russ, Ross.
史帝夫 大夫
Steve, sleeve.
拜托 哪有人叫大夫的
Okay, no one is named Sleeve.
菲比 你到底在瞎说什么啊
Phoebe, what the hell are you talking about?
抱歉 除了他们的名字以外
Other than their names being similar, I'm sorry
我没看出还有什么相似的地方
I do not see what you're seeing.
老实告诉你吧 是赌圣 不是赌胜
For your information, it's a card sharp, not a card shark.
你敢不敢再蠢点
You could not be more wrong.
你想怎么读就怎么读 但你仍然是错的
You could try, but you would not be successful.
我先倒杯咖啡 然后再回来看你们互插双眼
Okay, I'm gonna get some more coffee before the pinching and eye-poking begins.
我知道问题在哪儿了
I know what your problem is.
哦是吗 你知道?
Oh you do, do you?
你嫉妒了
Mm-hm, you're jealous.
嫉妒什么
Uh, of... of what?
你嫉妒我是个真正的医生
You're jealous because I'm a real doctor.
别闹了 你只是个牙龈医生
Hey, you're a doctor of gums.
那是能够研究的最小的人体器官
That's the smallest body part you can major in.
就像是第一天教你用牙线 第二天你就能毕业了
It's like, day one, floss. Day two, here's your diploma.
嘿 你给我听好了
Hey, you listen...
不 让我说完
No no, let me finish.
不 你让我说完
No, let me finish.
不 你让我说完...
No, you let me fini...
嗨
Hi.
咦
Ew.
噢 不
Ew, ew, ew.
乔伊走时有没有说打算怎么做
Did Joey say what he was gonna do when he left?
没
No.
我想他自己也不知道
I don't even think he knew.
你会为了一份好工作而献身吗
Hey, would you sleep with somebody to get a great job?
不清楚 得看和谁
I don't know. Who would I have to sleep with?
我
Me.
我为什么要跟你上床
Why would I have to sleep with you?
你要这工作就得听我的
It's my game. You want the job or not?
嗨      嘿
Hi.        Hey.
早上好
Good morning.
去哪儿
Where you going?
我要跟巴比去小木屋度周末 记得吗
Bobby and I are going away for the weekend, remember?
对哦
Oh.
拿那么多酒干嘛
What's with all the bottles of liquor?
怎么了 巴比又开始喝酒了吗
What's going on? Is... uh, Bobby drinking again?
不 这不是给他的 是给我准备的
Oh, no no, this is not for him, this is for me.
这样他既能继续戒酒
That way, he's still sober
而我又能觉得他关于鞋带的笑话好笑多了
but I find his stories about shoelaces more amusing.
天呐 他连敲门都这么无趣
Uh, God, even his knock is boring.
我马上就好
Hi, I'll be ready in just a second.
呃 我可以跟你谈一谈吗
Uh, could I talk to you a minute?
好啊
Sure.
这真的很难开口
This is really hard for me to say.
天呐 你又喝酒了吗
Oh, God, you fell off the wagon.
不 不是
Oh, no, no.
是关于你的
It's about you.
我怎么了
What about me?
我想你或许有酗酒问题
I think you may have a drinking problem.
不 这些是...
What, these?
擦伤口用的
No, these are, urmn, for cuts and scrapes.
听着 我现在没办法
Look, I am just not strong enough
扯入一段相互依赖的感情中
to be in a codependent relationship right now, okay?
该死
Oh, shoot.
无论如何 希望我们还能当朋友
Well, anyway, I hope we can be friends.
好吧
Okay.
保重
Take care.
嗯 你也是      再见
Okay, you too.        Bye.
怎么了
What happened?
我们...分手了
Well, we... we kinda broke up.
噢
Awwwwwwww.
这些酒谁要
Does anybody want these?
我要一瓶
I'll take one.
有时候我喜欢拿着这种东西 假装自己是个巨人
Sometimes I like to hold stuff like this and pretend I'm a giant.
嘿      复试结果怎么样
Hey.        Hey. How'd the callback go?
真不敢相信 我刚进去她就开始对我上下其手
Uh, it was unbelievable. I walked in there and she was all over me.
那你怎么做的
So, what'd you do?
我办不到
Well, I couldn't do it.
我告诉她我不想这样拿到那个角色
I told her I didn't want to get the part that way.
好样的      哇哦
Good for you!        Whoa!
等等 等等 但我离开她办公室之后
Oh, wait, wait, wait. But then after I left her office
她追我追到电梯 说要给我一个更重要的角色
she caught up with me at the elevator and offered me an even bigger part.
然后呢
So, and?
然后 各位面前站的是德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
So... you are now looking at Dr.Drake Ramoray, neurosurgeon
一位至少会在四集中出镜的神经外科医师!
recurring in at least four episodes!
太棒了!
All right!
好了 我要去洗澡了
All right, I gotta go shower
嗨...
Hi...
哦 嘿      嗨
Oh, hey.        Hi.
你们知道我被瑞秋甩了吧
I guess you guys heard Rachel dumped me.
是啊 真遗憾啊 老兄
Yeah, I'm sorry, man.
她只说是因为我会让她想起另外一个人
Oh, all she said was that I remind her too much of somebody.
你们知道那人是谁吗
You have any idea who she's talking about?
我知道 是鲍伯萨格特
Oh I do, it's... it's Bob Saget.
她讨厌他
She hates him.
嘿      嘿 茱莉
Hey.        Hey, Julie.
嘿 最近怎么样
Hey, how are you doing?
我不清楚 没有了罗斯 的确感觉很怪
Um, oh, I don't know. I mean, it's definitely weird not being with Ross
不过我觉得还不错
but, I guess I'm doing okay.
话说回来 我带了一些他的东西...
Actually, I've got some of his stuff that he um...
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧